어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri Martial Artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri Martial Artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi is here-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
in the center of the world to become
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! the strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes a life dazzle
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes a life dazzle
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight the utmost with the stillness
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
His eyes shined! Musashi!!
마음먹고 목숨을 걸어 천하의 검술의 달인 보쿠덴에 뭐가 어떻게 되든 제자로 해 달라고
Musashi has been asking Bokuden, the master Martial Artist of the century, to accept him as a pupil,
마음에 새긴 무사시의 열의의 과실이 보여 길고 쓰라린 수련이 시작되었다.
and his strong desire has finally got him to start a long and bitter training.
보쿠덴의 검의 극의를 배운 무사시는 살아남아 미야코 궁전에 간다.
Now, having learned the extreme art of swords from Bokuden, Musashi lives and heads for Miyako palace.
수도의 고조의 벤케이
Benkei from Gojo in the Capital
사무라이 씨!
Hey, Mr. Samurai!
미야코 궁전까지 가? 타고 가는 거 어때?
Are you going to Miyako palace? Why not ride?
말은 필요 없소.
I don't need a horse-dasu.
거절할 필요 없어. 저렴해!
No need to refuse. It's cheap after all!
걷는 쪽이 다리가 건강해지니 괜찮소.
Walking is good for the health of my legs, so I'll pass-dasu.
그런 말 하지 말고!
Don't say that!
무슨 문제 있소?
Anything wrong-dasu?
오줌! 이거 잠깐만!
Hurry! Hold this for a moment!
저기, 잠깐!
Hey, wait!
곤란해졌소...
I lose-dasu...
늦소...
He's being late-dasu...
벤케이
Benkei
오...
Hm...
꽤 좋아 보이는 말이구려.
He looks like a pretty nice horse.
확실히 좋은 말이오.
It surely is a good horse-dasu.
보면 볼수록 반하겠네. 미안하네만 잠시 타 보아도 괜찮겠나?
The more I look, more I fall in love. Let me try riding for a moment.
뭔 짓이오!
What are you doing-dasu?!
당연하다! 가지고 싶은 건 가져가는 게 내 방식이다!
Don't you see? Taking what I want is my principle!
야! 멈추시오!
Hey! Stop-dasu!
말도둑!
Horse thief!
멈추시오!
Stop!
시원하다!
I feel refreshed!
어라?
Huh?
뭔 일이야? 괜찮아?
What happened? Are you all right?
배, 배가 고파서 못 움직이오...
I cannot move because my stomach is empty-dasu...
내 말은 어쩌고?
What about my horse?
저기...
There...
네가 부주의한 거니까 네 잘못이야! 어쩔 거야!
You were careless so it's your fault! Do something!
설마 말도둑이라고는 생각하지 않았소...
I didn't think he would be a horse thief-dasu...
시끄러워! 어쨌든 니 잘못이야!
Shut up! It's your fault anyway!
뭐가 무슨 일이 있어도 꼭 변상해라!
Whatever happens, you must compensate me!
그... 그러겠소...
I will-dasu...
저기가 내 집이야.
That is my house.
자! 따라와.
Follow me!
혼자 사는 것이오?
Do you live alone?
그래. 불만이라도 있냐?
Right. Any problem?
문제는 없지만, 아버지나 형제나 없소?
Not really, but don't you have a dad or brother-dasu?
그런 건 아무래도 상관없어.
That doesn't really matter.
그보다! 미야코에서 일해서 정말 변상할 거지?
Anyway! Are you really going to compensate me by working in Miyako?
물론이오! 무예가 제일이 될 내가 못 할 일은 없소!
Of course! As the future number one Martial Artist, I can do anything-dasu!
무예가 제일?
Number one Martial Artist?
뭐가 이상하오?!
What's so funny-dasu?!
아, 아무것도 아냐. 미야코 궁전에 나쁜 놈도 많이 있으니까 조심해.
Nothing. There are lots of bad people in Miyako palace, so be careful.
걱정 마오. 그런 놈이 나타난다면 내가 처리해 보이겠소!
Don't worry. If such guy appears, I'll take care of him-dasu!
뭐가 이상하오?!
What's so funny-dasu?!
그래도 목검를 든 제일의 무예가라니 들은 적도 없어!
But, I never heard a number one Martial Artist with a wooden sword!
확실히 그게 맞는 말이오...
That is true-dasu...
미안. 필요없는 말을 했구나.
Sorry. I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
검술의 심오한 경지를 향해 배워 익히면 목검으로 진검승부를 볼 수도 있는 것이오.
It isn't impossible to have a real match by learning the innermost secrets of the techniques of sword-dasu.
그래도... 역시 진검이 있으면 좋겠소...
But still... I'd still like a real sword-dasu...
미안, 미안, 웃어버렸다!
Sorry, sorry, for laughing!
그렇게 검이 갖고 싶어?
Do you want a real sword that much?
그야 당연하오!
Of course I want-dasu!
그럼 좋은 곳을 소개해 줄게!
Then I know a good place!
따라와!
Follow me!
여, 여긴?
What happened?
어제 여기에서 전투가 있었어.
There was a fight yesterday here.
그럼 여기서 검을 주우라는 것이오?
Are you telling me to pick up a sword from here-dasu?
아까 검을 갖고 싶다 했잖아!
But you said you wanted one!
업신여기지 마시오! 검은 무사의 혼! 어느 세계에 길거리에서 혼을 주워 쓰는 자가 있소이까!
Don't look down on me-dasu! A sword is the spirit of Martial Artist!
Where in the world is a Martial Artist who uses a found spirit-dasu?
마음에 들었어! 좋아, 너 마음에 들어!
Good job! Great, I like your attitude!
너라면 분명히 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 될 수 있을 거야!
You will definitely manage to be the number one Martial Artist of Jipangu!
-그, 그렇소?
-당연하지! 힘내라!
-Do you really think so-dasu?
-Of course! Keep up the good work!
알겠소!
Thank you-dasu!
이곳은 미야코 궁전. 황실이 있는 이 마을은 화려함으로 가득 차 있었다.
This is Miyako palace. Brilliance was filling this village where the Royal Household is there.
검을 손에 넣고, 잃은 말을 변상하기 위해 무사시는 일을 찾아 걸어다녔다.
To get a sword and compensate for the lost horse, Musashi walked around to get a job.
아기 돌볼 분 구함
높은 급료 우대
공정회계
가내안전
자세한 정보는 왼쪽으로
Looking for a Babysitter
High Salary Guaranteed
Honest Billing
Peaceful Household
For more information, please go to left
아이 돌보는 일이오...
Babysitting-dasu...
츠카하라 보쿠덴에게 직접 전수받은 이 내가 이걸 하기에는 꼴이 말이 아니오만...
Even I know it is pathetic to do this, after learning from Tsukahara Bokuden-dasu, but...
뭐든 하겠다는 정신은 바뀌지 않소!
I am desperate enough-dasu!
착하지! 착하오!
Good boy!
아... 보람없소...
How fruitless-dasu...
저건!
That must be...
코지로!
Kojirō!
아, 안 돼! 이런 모습! 제일의 수치오!
Not now! Being in this shape is the number one embarrassment-dasu!
울지 마라...
Don't cry...
저 자... 무사시 닮았군.
That man looks like Musashi.
끈질기오!
So persistent-dasu!
이게! 이렇게 되어야 한다면!
Bastard! If you're not going to stop...
정체를 보여라!
Show yourself!
아니잖아.
He isn't.
당연하지.
Of course.
무사시가 아기 돌보는 일 따위를 하고 있을 리가 없지.
No way Musashi's babysitting.
위험했소...
So close-dasu...
착한 아이들이오!
Good babies-dasu!
좋소! 이번엔 내 특기를 보여드리겠소!
Now! Time for my specialties-dasu!
이걸 어쩌오...
What should I do-dasu...
야! 잘도 내 아이들을 울렸겠다!
Hey! How dare you make my babies cry!
미안하오!
Sorry-dasu!
역시 아이들 돌보는 일은 내게는 맞지 않소...
Babysitting is definitely not for me-dasu...
파수꾼 구함!
지금이야말로 당신의
재능을 살릴 기회!
자세한 건 이쪽으로
Guard Wanted!
The time has come to
utilize your talent!
More information on the left
나에게 맞는 일이란...
What would be my aptitude...?
어?
Huh?
파수꾼 구함!
지금이야말로 당신의
재능을 살릴 기회!
자세한 건 이쪽으로
Guard Wanted!
The time has come to
utilize your talent!
More information on the left
파수꾼 구함!
지금이야말로 당신의
재능을 살릴 기회!
자세한 건 이쪽으로
Guard Wanted!
The time has come to
utilize your talent!
More information on the left
이것이오, 이것!
This is it-dasu! This!
이 아닌 듯 하오...
...isn't it-dasu...
주인님 나가신다! 청소는 무엇보다도 깨끗하게!
The master will be checking out! Make this place as clean as possible!
예!
Got it!
이렇게는 아가들 돌보는 일보다도 처참하오...
This is even more miserable than babysitting-dasu...
도와주시오!
Help me-dasu!
이래서는 또 모가지오!
I'll be fired again like this-dasu!
무사시는 일을 잘 하지 못했다.
Musashi wasn't good at working.
잘 하지를 못하고 있소...
I'm not doing well-dasu...
무사시 형!
Musashi bro!
켄타! 어라, 그 말은 어디서 구했소?
Kenta! Hey, where did you get that horse-dasu?
일단 말 하나는 있어야 먹고 사니까.
I need a horse to live, you know.
렌탈 말이야.
It's a rented horse.
렌탈 말? 빌렸소? 돈은?
Rented horse? Did you borrow-dasu? What about the money?
있을까 말까 한 걸레까지 털어냈어.
I had to sell even a rag.
그래서 나 한푼도 없어.
Because of that I'm broke.
언제 보상할 거야?
When are you going to compensate?
다양한 일을 하고 있으니 곧이오.
I'm doing various jobs, so it won't take long-dasu!
꼭 갚아! 부탁해!
Do pay back! I believe in you!
알겠소! 밑고 맡기소!
I know-dasu! Leave it to me-dasu!
부탁이야!
Please!
무사시의 아르바이트는 원하는 대로 잘 되어가지 않았다.
Musashi's part time job wasn't going well as he wanted.
그러나 무사시는 쭉 끈질기게 포기하지 않고 켄타의 말 변상을 위해,
But in order to compensate Kenta's horse, Musashi was tenacious and never gave up.
그리고 꿈에서도 보는 진검을 위해 밤낮 구분없이 다양한 일에 힘썼다.
Also, he worked all day and night to get a real sword that he always see in his dream.
배고프오...
So hungry-dasu...
아니야, 참아야 하오.
No, I must endure-dasu.
오츠루 씨 요즘 무엇하며 살지 궁금하오...
I wonder how's Otsuru doing-dasu...
나, 이제 곧 진검을 사게 되오.
I will buy a real sword soon enough-dasu.
진검을 손에 넣으면 어떤 무예가에도 지지 않는 제일이 되는 날이 멀지 않소.
When I get a real sword, the day of becoming the number one Martial Artist who never loses to others will get even closer.
그렇게 되면 꼭 맞이하러 가겠소.
And when I become one, I'll take you as a wife.
오츠루 씨...
Otsuru...
야! 무슨 짓이오!
Hey! What are you doing?!
무사시는 검을 손에 넣을 수 있을 것인가. 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Will Musashi manage to put his hands on a real sword? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
이야! 드디어 다 모았소!
Yeah! I finally saved up enough-dasu!
이걸로 검도 구매하고 빚도 갚겠소!
I'll buy a sword and repay him-dasu!
도검집
전문점
SWORD STORE
SPECIALTY SHOP
누구 있소?
Excuse me-dasu.
어서오세요.
Welcome.
꽤 좋은 검이오...
This is good sword-dasu!
오, 눈이 높으시군요.
Oh, you have a discerning eye!
이 검 얼마나 하오?
How much does this cost-dasu?
음... 이 정도이오.
About this.
와, 저렴하오! 2문이오?
It's really cheap! Only two mons-dasu?
(4000문 = 16주 = 4분 = 1양)
(4000 mon = 16 shu = 4 bu = 1 ryo)
심한 농담을! 20양이오.
You're joking! It's 20 ryos.
20양?!
20 ryos?!
어라, 무리인가요?
Is it too much?
아니오. 검은 무사의 생명. 좋은 것이라면 아낌없이 돈을 쓰겠으나...
Nope. A sword is the spirit of Martial Artist. I'd spend money unsparingly for a good sword, but...
조금만 더 저렴한 것을 원하오.
I'd like a cheaper one-dasu.
그럼 이건 어떤가요?
Then how is this?
이거라면 깎아서 25분!
With discount, it only costs 25 bus!
이거라면 어때요? 1양 2분!
How's this? 1 ryo 2 bus!
아직아직!
More!
단돈 1양!
Just 1 ryo!
좀만 더!
A bit more!
정 안 되겠으면 9부 어떱니까?
If that doesn't work, how is 9 bus?
다시 비싸졌잖소!
I don't fall for that!
당신, 정말로 살 생각은 있어요?
Are you going to buy or not?
물론이오.
Of course-dasu.
알겠습니다.
All right.
이보다 저렴한 검은 없어요!
This is the cheapest sword here!
단돈 3분!
Only 3 bus!
2부 반 되오?
Can you make it 2 bus and a half-dasu?
드디어 손에 넣었소.
Finally I got one-dasu.
하늘이 되었소!
I've became the sky-dasu!
(도움 안 되는 손님을 보내고 좋은 손님을 바라는 의미에서 소금을 뿌림)
(He throws salt in hope of keeping away bad customers and attracting good customers)
다시는 오지 마라!
Never come again!
이야! 진검은 확실히 무게가 다르오!
A real sword weights differently-dasu!
왠지 갑자기 신분이 높아진 기분이 드오.
I feel like I just became a person of high rank-dasu.
이 광택.
What brilliance!
이 녀석은 괜찮게 획득한 것이오.
I got this fair and square-dasu.
꽤 괜찮은 것 같소.
Looks like a pretty good one-dasu.
저렴하게 구입했으니 켄타네 말 변상도 가능하겠소!
Since I got in a low price, I'll can pay for Kenta's horse too-dasu!
딱 충분하오.
Right on the mark-dasu!
이게 있으면 코지로한테서 숨으며 아르바이트한 가치가 보이는 것이오!
With this, I see the value of doing part-time jobs, hiding from Kojirō-dasu!
코지로! 각오하시오!
Kojirō! Prepare yourself!
그 자이오.
That guy-dasu.
그럼 벤케이가 말도둑이었다는 거야?
So you're saying Benkei was the horse thief?
켄타, 그 사람 알고 있소?
Kenta, do you know that guy-dasu?
하나, 둘... 아, 유명하고말고. 좋아! 이거면 됐어. 확실히 받았어.
One, two... Yeah, he's famous. Good! This will do. Thank you for compensation.
이제 말끔해졌소. 그건 그렇고, 벤케이에 대해서...
I feel clear-headed-dasu. Anyway, about Benkei...
아, 말도 안 되는 놈한테 걸렸구나. 나도 들은 바이지만...
Yeah, you were trapped by an unthinkable bastard. I only heard about him, but...
녀석은 미야코 고조 다리 위에 홀연 나타나 다리를 건너는 사무라이를 노려 승부를 봐 이기면 칼을 빼앗는다고 해.
It is said that he appears on the bridge of Gojo of Miyako,
and he targets the samurais to have a match and take their swords as booty.
지금까지 999명의 사무라이가 칼을 빼앗겼다고 해.
It is told that 999 samurais lost their swords until now.
대단한 녀석이오...
That guy is something-dsu...
그래서 이제 어쩔 거야, 너?
So what are you gonna do from now on?
도전해야지? 벤케이한테?
A challenge? Against Benkei?
아, 알고 있었소?
Di- did you already know-dasu?
당연하지! 너니까 말야. 그만하라 하도 안 들을 거잖아.
Of course! It's you after all. You're not going to stop even if I stop you.
그렇게 대단한 놈이라면 상대로서 부족함이 없소.
To know he's that dreadful, he is a perfect opponent for me-dasu.
반드시 이겨 보이겠소!
I'll definitely win!
당장 일어날 일이구나. 뭐, 벤케이는 상대를 죽이진 않으니까 괜찮나?
He's doing this right now... It shouldn't be harmful since Benkei doesn't kill his opponent, I guess?
벤케이! 연속 도검 강탈꾼 벤케이, 있소?
Benkei! Serial sword robber Benkei, are you there-dasu?
무예가 제일에 한 발 가까워진 미야모토 마을의 무사시가 상대해 주겠소!
Musashi from Miyamoto village has just taken another step to the number one Martial Artist, and he will face you-dasu!
승부볼 테니 나오시오!
Come out and have a match-dasu!
없는 것이오?
Is nobody here-dasu?
안 나올 것이오?
Aren't you going to come out-dasu?
그럼 이 무사시가 두렵다는 것으로 받아들이겠소!
Then I'll take that as you fear me, Musashi!
정말 입만 살아가지고..
He's all talk.
싸우지 않고 이겼소.
I won without fighting-dasu.
깔보지 마라.
Don't make fun of me.
왜 이 몸이 도망쳐야만 하는 것인가? 멍청한 놈.
Why do I have to run away? You idiot.
벤케이! 등장!
Benkei's here!
나오셨소, 벤케이! 무사시가 상대해 주겠소!
You came out, Benkei! Musashi will face you-dasu!
오, 너는 그 때 꼬맹이냐.
Oh, you're that kid from before.
뭣이? 검으로 모자라 말까지 빼앗는 것은 비겁하기 짝이 없소!
What?! To steal not only swords but also horses, you're very cowardly!
알겠소? 전력으로 승부를 보겠소!
Got it? Let's have a match to death-dasu!
관둬라, 관둬! 오늘밤은 기념할 만한 천번째의 밤.
Give it up and shoo! Today is the monumental thousandth night.
그 상대는 실력있는 거물로 정했다.
I decided the opponent to be an important person.
자! 얘야! 얼렁 비켜라!
Now, get lost, kid!
닥치시오! 난 아이가 아니오! kensei 보쿠덴의 가르침을 받은 제일의 제자이오!
Shut up! I am not a kid! I am the only pupil of Bokuden, the master Martial Artist!
녀석, 꽤 하네!
He's pretty good!
어떻소! 물러나지 않은 걸 후회하지 마시오!
How's this? Don't regret doing this!
시끄러운 애새끼가!
What a noisy kid!
산 지 얼마 안 된 칼이...
I bought this sword today and...
녀석, 싼 걸 샀구나.
I guess he bought a cheap one.
마, 말도 안 돼...
No... no way...
설마 그 도검집이 나에게 무딘 검을...
That sword store must have sold me a blunt sword!
젠장!
Damn!
벌써 여기까지군. 게임 오버다.
I see it's settled. Game over.
무엇보다도 나에게 없는 것을 가져갈 생각이니까.
I was going to take the one I don't have after all.
이렇게 됐으면 삶든지 태우던지 맘대로 하시오!
I don't care anymore even if you boil or set me on fire literally!
방해하지 마라! 얼렁 비켜라!
Don't interfere! Just get lost!
멈춰라.
Stop.
뭔가?
What is it?
그 허리에 있는 것을 가져가겠다.
I will take what you have on your waist.
오? 이걸?
You mean this?
그쪽의 금 야태도, 참으로 나의 천 번째로 어울리는 것.
Your gold large war sword will be a perfect fit for the thousandth item of my collection.
순순히 주지 않겠는가?
Wouldn't you obediently pass it over?
싫다.
No way.
그런가. 그렇다면... 얻어서 내 것으로 만들 때까지!
I see. If then... we'll fight until I get that!
우시와카
Ushikawa
그대가 밤마다 고조의 다리를 더럽힌다 하는, 거대한 바보의 벤케이군.
I see that you're the big idiot who brings disgrace upon the bridge of Gojo every night.
뭐라?
What?
미야코를 휩쓰는 고얀놈, 내가 퇴치하겠다!
I'll get rid of the scoundrel that rampages in Miyako!
뭐시라?!
What?!
놀리지 마라!
Don't make me laugh!
뭔 일이냐?
What's the problem?
젠장... 웃기지 마라!
Damn... don't fool around!
뭐야?!
What?!
어떻냐. 내가 어떻게든 원하는 대로 되던가?
How's that? Did you manage to make me pass the sword?
뭔 이까짓 걸로...
That's insignificant.
져, 졌다. 제가 졌습니다.
I lost, as you see.
오늘 밤의 장물, 더욱 수련해야겠구나.
Tonight's useless thing should train more.
기, 기다려 주십시오!
Please wait!
일단 존함을!
Tell me your name!
내 이름을 알아서 어쩔 생각인가?
What are you going to do with my name?
아무쪼록 이 벤케이를 깨달음의 다리로 부탁드립니다!
I beg of you, please lead Benkei to the bridge of enlightenment.
왜 졌는지 알기 전까지는 만족하지 못하는구나.
I see that you will remain unsatisfied before knowing why you lost.
예!
Right!
그럼 가르쳐 드리겠소.
Then I'll let you know.
나는 우시와카.
I am Ushiwaka.
우시와카라 하오.
You may call me Ushiwaka.
우시와카라...
Ushiwaka...
기, 기다려 주십시오!
Please wait!
제발! 부디! 벤케이를!
Please! I beg of you! Have Benkei!
미야코 궁전에 나쁜 사람 많다고 했잖아.
I told you there are many bad people in Miyako palace.
아, 알고 있소.
I know-dasu.
힘내. 나도 혼자서 어떻게든 힘내며 살고 있으니까.
Get a grip. I'm trying my best alone.
나... 나...
I... I...
벤케이에게 진 게 아니오!
I didn't lose to Benkei!
모든 건... 모든 건 이것 잘못이오!
Everything... everything is the fault of this thing!
무사시는 또 세상의 넓음을 miyomotte 체험하게 되었다. 그것을 알고 있는가, 아닌가?
Musashi experienced the wideness of the world again ~ly. Does he know that or not?
그러나! 이런 일로 꺾일 무사시가 아니다! 가라! 나아가라, 무사시여!
But! Musashi isn't going to be discouraged because of such things. Go! Advance, Musashi!
그것이 사내의 길이다!
That is the road of man to stage.
허공의 주머니에 달이
Sometimes the moon jumps over
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
the pocket of the empty sky
큰 소리로 웃으면
Laugh loudly and
내일에는 아침이 와
a morning will come tomorrow
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Don't care too much about losing
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
Keep doing! Go for it!
맨손은 강해
A bare hand is strong
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
That's how life is! Look, a chance
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
follows us wagging its tail!
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
That's how future also is! Look, tomorrow
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
요시오카 도장의 젊은 선생, 세쥬로를 쓰러뜨린 나는 제자들에게 쫒기는 신세에.
I am being chased by pupils, after taking down a young teacher of Yoshioka Dōjō.
그 때 구해준 분은 료마 씨.
At that moment, Ryoma appeared and saved me.
그러나 이 사람, 달아나는 것도 훌륭한 병법의 하나라고 하오.
This person says that running away is one of the superb tactics-dasu.
이런 유연한 무예가는 처음 만나오.
I never met such easygoing Martial Artist-dasu.
다음 이야기! 료마는 혼자 바람 속에
Next story! Ryoma is Alone in the Wind
질풍노도의 활약을 보시오!
Be sure to check out the stormy action-dasu!
다음 이야기
료마는 혼자 바람 속에
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Ryoma is Alone in the Wind
Look forwards for it!